Hello.
こんにちは
It's cute.
可愛いですね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
It's pretty amazing.
結構素晴らしいです
It's amazing.
素晴らしいです
Often said.
よく言われる
People often say that I'm cute.
よく言われるでしょ、可愛いって
It is said.
言われます
You're honest.
正直なんですね
In Miyagi.
宮城で
Your skin is very white.
肌めっちゃ白いですね
That is also said.
それも言われます
Don't you do any exercise?
運動とかしないんですか?
For exercise, we go for walks together.
運動は、仲良く散歩とか行きます
stroll?
散歩?
Alone?
一人で?
Alone.
一人で
Isn't it a pet or something?
ペットとかじゃなくて?
Yes, I'll go alone.
はい、一人で行きます
I do things like take walks.
散歩とかするんですね
I will.
します
Is it your hobby?
趣味ですか?
I go there every night, so I think it's a hobby.
毎日夜行くんで、趣味だと思います
night?
夜?
How do you decide to go for a walk regularly?
定期的っていうか、どういう思いつきで散歩ってするんですか?
I've never done it, so I don't really know.
したことないんで、ちょっと分かんないです
I guess I'll take a walk then.
じゃあ散歩しようみたいな
I don't do any exercise or muscle training, so walking is the easiest way to get my body moving.
運動、筋トレとかしないから、体動かしたい時に 散歩が一番楽
That's why, and because I love music,
だから、 あと音楽が好きだから、
I'm walking at night.
夜に歩いてます
I see.
なるほど
If it was night, you might as well put it in the sun.
夜だったら日におけとかもしないです
Is it like walking, like running?
ランニングみたいな感じで散歩するって感じか?
Running makes me tired, so I go for a walk.
ランニングは疲れるから、散歩します
But I do things like that with people I don't know.
でも知らない人とそういうことするけど、
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It's probably okay.
たぶん大丈夫
Are you okay.
大丈夫
It's late there.
そこは遅いね
It's late, isn't it?
遅いですね
It's not too late.
遅くないですよ
It's late, isn't it?
遅いでしょ
What are you doing to tell the number of keeps?
伝えるキープ数は何かしてるの?
I haven't really done anything.
あんま何もしてないですし
Don't you eat rice?
ご飯は食べない?
I eat a lot of rice.
ご飯めっちゃ食べます
yes?
そう?
I eat a lot.
めっちゃ食べます
What do you like?
何が好きなんですか?
Sushi.
お寿司
Please sub-shiromi.
サブシロミしてください
What do you like about sushi?
お寿司のネタ何が好きなんですか?
Sushi...
寿司は...
It's sushi.
寿司です
Do you go out to eat often?
よく食べに行くんですか?
Just keep your hands on it.
そのままベッタリ手ついてね
Look at your butt.
お尻つきだしてごらん
Just turn that face towards me.
その顔だけこっち向いて
Do you often wear top pants?
よく上パンツ履くの?
Is there a lot of white?
白が多いの?
Show me your face.
顔見せて
You have a really nice butt.
めっちゃいいお尻してるね
She has a really nice butt.
めっちゃいいお尻してる
Look this way.
こっち向いてごらん
You can stand.
立っていいや
Lift up your skirt and show me your panties.
自分でスカート上げてパンツ見せてごらん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's just right.
ちょうどいいじゃん
This is what happens when you play sports.
ス ンポしてたらこうなるの
You don't eat rice, right?
ご飯食べないでしょ?
I eat a lot.
いっぱい食べます
That won't happen, right?
そうならないでしょ普通
I've never done anything.
何もやったことない
tell me.
教えて
Do you say nice things to women?
女にいいとかするの?
no.
いや
do?
する?
do.
する
How many times together?
一緒に何回?
If you want to.
したくなったら
Once together, more.
一緒に一度、もっと
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Very soft
めっちゃ柔らかい
hey.
ね
Some pants.
何 かパンツ
scene.
シーン
Does this feel good?
この気持ちいい?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
what?
何?
Stavator.
スタベーターすわ
Remove the bottom.
下抜いて
Take off your pants.
パンツ抜いてごらん
I can't go down.
下抜けない
Was it?
だったの?
Are you home yet?
まだ帰ってる?
I'm still home.
まだ帰ってる
That's a nice style.
いいスタイルだね
I opened my legs again.
また足開いたからね
Yeah, smooth.
うん、ツルツル
Look at your butt.
お尻抜けてごらん
Go to your pet.
ペットのほう行って
Get on top of me.
上乗って
Get your butt out.
お尻抜けて
For both hands.
両手の場合に
What should I do now?
もうちょっと、どうしようか
Just stick it out in front of you.
前突き出してごらん
Stick your butt out.
前突き出して、お尻
Come perfectly.
バッチリ来て
Of course.
もちろんね
Try being MJ.
MJになってごらん
Perfect
バッチリ
Come.
来 て
Just stick it out in front of you.
前突き出してごらん
Get your butt out.
お尻抜けて